<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam &amp; Moore</title>
    <description>Hi there! This is the personal website of yours truly, Sam Moore. I am a software engineer living and working in New York City. I spend my free time reading and contemplating how to be better at writing software and mentoring other engineers.
</description>
    <link>http://samandmoore.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://samandmoore.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 14:51:30 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 14:51:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Direction, Betterment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After the demise of Group Commerce, I went on the hunt to find a new start-up job. I found Betterment, and I couldn’t be happier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it’s been a while since I’ve posted anything substantial about myself. In June, my employer, Group Commerce, fail-merged (the market dried up and they merged with a competitior), and they decided to let nearly everyone go. Before everything collapsed, there were internal whisperings of what was going to happen, so I started looking for a new place to work. Having realized that working in the start-up space was a good fit for me, I focused my search in that sector of the job market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found a few companies that I was interested in, and I began frantically prepping for interviews by asking basically every smart person I knew to quiz me. After talking to a few places, I decided to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterment.com&quot;&gt;Betterment&lt;/a&gt;. I heard about it about a month earlier from a good friend that I worked with at Group Commerce. Betterment provides a personal finance tool for investing one’s money in the simplest, most elegant way possible. Elevator pitch: Sign up online; link your checking account; create a goal for what you might want to do with your money in x years; set up automatic deposts; and you’re invested in a diversified market portfolio. My friend happened to have already spoken to Betterment about a position, and was contemplating accepting it or one of a few other offers he had. He convinced me to go out for some drinks with the Engineering team and see what I thought, and boy am I glad that I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went with some soon-to-be-former co-workers to meet the Betterment people for drinks, and I had the opportunity just talk shop a little bit. It was awesome to be able to meet with a group of possible future co-workers in a neutral environment before going in for an interview. It really removed a lot of the fear and uncertainty from the equation. I loved what I heard in conversations that night, and so I decided to schedule an interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interview was a great experience. I spent a few hours at the Betterment office, and I met with 5 or so people. They all challenged me to prove how I would be a great fit for the company, and, as it turns out, I did a good enough job to earn myself an offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That all happened back in May. Since then, I’ve accepted, taken a month off the spend with my wonderful girlfriend, and started working there. I have to say, after working at Group Commerce, getting to know and love that environment, I am surprised at how much I love working at Betterment. I was hoping that it would be at least as good of an environment as Group Commerce, but it has proven to be even better. I am fortunate that in addition to myself, a group of other Group Commerce engineers also came along for the ride at Betterment. That undoubtedly has made the trasition to a new company easier, but I have already made some real friends at Betterment, and I continue to grow those relationships every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could not be happier with where I’ve landed. Now I am doing everything in my power to make Betterment a hugely successful company…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… fingers crossed!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 22:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://samandmoore.com/2013/08/25/new-direction-betterment.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://samandmoore.com/2013/08/25/new-direction-betterment.html</guid>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        <category>work</category>
        
        <category>software</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>switched my DNS to DNSimple</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to drop dreamhost and switch to DNSimple for registering and configuring the DNS for my websites. The price is right and the UX is super smooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I decided that I was going to move my blog to a simple static site generator
instead of something complicated like rails, I also decided to check out hosting
it somewhere that can handle the amount of traffic it receives… none. As such,
I am going with a free account on heroku. We shall see how this experiment turns out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE 2016-02-21&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turned out great. I’m still loving this choice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 22:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://samandmoore.com/2013/06/03/switched-my-dns-to-dnsimple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://samandmoore.com/2013/06/03/switched-my-dns-to-dnsimple.html</guid>
        
        <category>web</category>
        
        <category>hosting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Laura&#39;s broken ankle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sadly, last night Laura broke her ankle. She was taking out the garbage when everything went wrong.
She took one wrong step and it was game over for her evening and her ankles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laura broke her ankle :(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE 2016-02-21&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s entirely back to normal :) It didn’t take 3 years, but I saw this
post again and decided that it just sounded too grim.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:43:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://samandmoore.com/2013/05/23/lauras-broken-ankle.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://samandmoore.com/2013/05/23/lauras-broken-ankle.html</guid>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
